I have stopped eating unhealthy things.
Now if we talk about burger, its taste is also
healthy.  The chicken inside
it is also healthy and the letters
are healthy anyway.  So it means that this
entire burger is healthy.  So I
ordered two.  Brother, see
in front of your eyes the same things which I have told you are absolutely
healthy.  Let's quickly
start eating and all that because I'm
very hungry right now.  Firstly, the
healthy thing does
not even taste good.  We have to survive by adding ketchup.
If we talk about the
taste of the burger, it is just average.  Well
brother, I have had breakfast early in the morning.
Now let's go to college.  Brother, I have to
go to college and get my admission done now,
but I am unable to understand which
subject I should take. Tell me all of you. It was
very hot after coming home, so I thought that I should
drink some cold Marish. It is not at
all a high recommendation from my side.
If I did not like it, then
why would I use it for the entire month, and that too every
day. It is finished now. First, let me prepare food etc.,
after that I will order Matches again for the
next month. Today I again
made such a sol with the help of milk only, which
we can eat with blood. It is
almost ready for us, but till the
milk would get spoiled,
I toasted the blood. Believe me, this
sol turns out to be very yummy.
If not, its recipe is given in the previous vlog.